Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
- Księgarnia Polska w Pary?u (Paris), April 1978-Feb 1984; n.d. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Contains 2 catalogs / price lists and a typewritten letter, 1 page, 3 items total. In Polish mostly.
- Księgarnia Polska (Wien), 1985-1998; n.d. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, postcards, and related documents, 24 items total. Some items are with marks and notes. Multilingual.
- Księgarz, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Contains a photocopy of an article, 6 pages, in Polish.
- Kubon and Sagner [1 of 49], 1969, 1972, 1974 [?], 1976 [?], 1980-1982 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 15 items. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Kubon and Sagner [2 of 49], 1982-1983 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 20 items (including doubles). (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Kubon and Sagner [3 of 49], 1983 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 5 items. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [4 of 49], 1983 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 6 items. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [5 of 49], 1984 [?] The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 4 items. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [6 of 49], 1984 [?]The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 5 items. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [7 of 49], 1984, March-Sept The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 17 items. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [8 of 49], 1984, Oct-Nov The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 17 items. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Kubon and Sagner [9 of 49], 1985, Feb-May The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 17 items. (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Kubon and Sagner [10 of 49], 1985, July-Dec; 1985 [?] The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 22 items. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [11 of 49], 1986, Jan-Feb The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 21 items. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [12 of 49], 1986, March-April The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 33 items. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [13 of 49], 1986, May-June The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 24 items. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [14 of 49], 1986, July-August The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 26 items. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [15 of 49], 1986, Sept The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 12 items. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [16 of 49], 1986, Oct-Nov The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 28 items. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [17 of 49], Dec 1986-1987 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 19 items. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [18 of 49], 1987, Jan-April The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 26 items. (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [19 of 49], 1987, May-July The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 21 items. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [20 of 49], 1987, August-Oct The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 19 items. (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [21 of 49], 1987, Nov-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 21 items. (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [22 of 49], 1988; Jan-May 1988 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 22 items. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [23 of 49], 1988, June-August The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 25 items. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [24 of 49], 1988, Sept-Oct; 1988 [?] The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 15 items. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [25 of 49], 1988, Nov-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 23 items. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [26 of 49], 1989, Jan-Feb; 1989 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 19 items. (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [27 of 49], 1989, March-April The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 16 items. (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [28 of 49], 1989, May The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 11 items. (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [29 of 49], 1989, June-August The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 19 items. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Kubon and Sagner [30 of 49], 1989, Sept-Oct The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 16 items. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [31 of 49], 1989, Nov-Dec; 1990, Jan-Feb The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 17 items. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [32 of 49], 1990, March-June The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual.The folder contains 22 items. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [33 of 49], 1990, July The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 14 items. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [34 of 49], 1990, Sept-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 13 items. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [35 of 49], 1991, Jan-May The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 17 items. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [36 of 49], 1991, June-July The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 13 items. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [37 of 49], 1991, August-Nov The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 16 items. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [38 of 49], 1992, March-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 19 items. (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [39 of 49], 1993, March-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 21 items. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [40 of 49], 1994; 1994, March-Sept The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 16 items. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [41 of 49], 1994, Oct-Dec The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 20 items. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [42 of 49], 1995, March-May The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 15 items. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [43 of 49], 1995, July-Dec; 1996, Feb-April The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 15 items. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [44 of 49], 1996, July-Dec; 1997; 1997, April-July The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual.The folder contains 24 items. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Kubon and Sagner [45 of 49], 1997, August-Nov; 1998 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 18 items. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner [46 of 49], 1998, Jan-Dec; Jan 1999 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 11 items. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Kubon and Sagner [47 of 49], 06.23.2000; March 2005 The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Kubon and Sagner [48 of 49], n.d. The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual. The folder contains 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Kubon and Sagner [49 of 49], n.d. The collection contains catalogs / price lists and photocopies of them, related correspondence, other documents / photocopies of documents, etc. Some items are damaged to some extent and / or with handwritten marks, notes, etc. The collection is multilingual.The folder contains 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Kulakov, Valery, "Russica Publishers" (Germany / Sweden), 06.06.2001; 01.22.2002; 12.12.2002; 03.09.2007; 08.03.2008 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog (with handwritten notes / marks, in Russian), a postcard with an envelope, a typewritten letter with an envelope and related typewritten materials, and 3 e-mail printouts, 3 pages.
- Kultiúra (Budapest, Hungary), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog / price list, in English and Hungarian.
- Lang, Peter (Germany), 1986-1987; Summer 1998-Spring 1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  Contains 3 catalogs with enclosures and a handwritten note.
- Lavka chitatelia (Allston, MA), Jan 1997 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  Contains 2 identical typewritten catalogs.
- Legutko, Z. Michael (New Jersey - New York), May 7, 1988-Sept [?] 1992; n.d. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  Contains 7 catalogs, some with enclosures and / or annotated, in Polish and English mostly.See also: "Lipert Gallery".
- Lemkin, Mikhail (San Francisco), Feb 15, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  Contains a press release, 2 pages.
- Letopis' periodichesikh izdanii, Sept 1981-June 1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  Contains typewritten catalogs and related materials (or photocopies of them), probably incomplete, 15 pages total. In Russian mostly.
- Lettres Slaves [1 of 5], 02.09.1984-05.11.1986; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs, correspondence, photocopies of clippings and other related materials. Multilingual (in Polish mostly). The folder includes 6 items.
- Lettres Slaves [2 of 5], 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs no.1-10, 16 items total (including doubles). Some catalogs are annotated and / or with enclosures.
- Lettres Slaves [3 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs no.13-14, 16-19; 9 items total (including doubles).
- Lettres Slaves [4 of 5], 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  Contains catalogs no.20-21, 4 items total (including doubles).
- Lettres Slaves [5 of 5], 1994; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs no.22-24 and a leaflet; 7 items total (including doubles).
- Lexicon - Księgarnia Wysyiłkowa (Warsaw, Poland), April 1992-1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Contains 4 catalogs, some of them annotated; in Polish mostly.
- Libella (Paris), April 1983-Dec 1989; Spring 1991; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  Contains typewritten catalogs and photocopies of clippings, 41 items total. In Polish and French mostly.
- Liber (Zagreb), n.d. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  Contains a catalog in Serbo-Croatian [?].
- Liberty Publishing House, Inc. (New York), n.d. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  Contains flyers and press releases, 7 items total. In Russian and English.
- Librairie Ancienne et Moderne - 1 Chmeljuk (Paris), 06.27.1978-04.13.1979; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  Contains typewritten catalogs, correspondence, etc., 12 items total. Some materials are annotated. Multilingual.
- Librairie Chevrenille-Renard (Brussels, Belgium), n.d. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  Contains 2 typewritten catalogs, multilingual.
- Librairie des Cinq Continents (Paris), 11.28.1978 [?] (Box 38, Folder 14)
  Contains an annotated catalog, in Russian mostly.
- La Librairie du Globe (Paris), 1991 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog with enclosures, in French and Russian.
- Librairie E. de Sialsky (Paris), Oct 1930; 08.16.1985 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  Contains a catalog (in Russian, pre-1917 spelling) and a clipping (in French). Slightly damaged.
- Librairie M. Slatkine (Geniève), Oct 1930; 08.16.1985 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  Contains a catalog (in Russian, pre-1917 spelling).
- Librairie Polonaise (Paris), 1835; 1983-1989; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  Contains catalogs, photocopies of catalogs and clippings, a questionnaire; 14 items total. In Polish and French mostly.
- Library Microfilms (Palo Alto, California), 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  Contains a photocopy of a typewritten price list. In Russian and Ukrainian (in Latin transliteration).
- Libreria Adolfo Linardi (Montevideo, Uruguay), Oct 1982-July [?] 1983; n.d. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  Contains correspondence, photocopies of price lists / lists of books, and other related materials. 8 items total.
- Lindsay and Howes Booksellers (England), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  Contains a photocopy of a typewritten price list, 2 pages..
- Lipert Gallery [1 of 4] (NJ-NY), Oct 1981-Nov 1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  Contains auction lists and catalogs with enclosures, 11 items total. Multilingual.See also: Legutko, Z. Michael.
- Lipert Gallery [2 of 4] (NJ-NY), Jan 1987-Jan 1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  Contains a questionnaire, correspondence, typewritten and published catalogs, 7 items total.
- Lipert Gallery [3 of 4] (NJ-NY), Jan 1990-Oct 1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  Contains action catalogs with enclosures, 8 items, some are annotated. Multilingual. Includes also a regular book catalog.
- Lipert Gallery [4 of 4] (NJ-NY), Jan 1993-June 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  Contains action catalogs with enclosures, 6 items. Multilingual. Includes also a regular book catalog.
- The Lists of Slavic book dealers, Oct 1974; n.d. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  Contains a photocopy of the AATSEEL newsletter (a fragment?), 2 pages, and a torn-out back cover of a catalog with handwritten notes / marks.
- Liturgica (Paris), 06.03.1988-09.25.1989; n.d. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  Contains photocopies of handwritten price lists, 16 items total. In Russian.
- Litwinowicz, V.N. (NY), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  Contains a typewritten price list, 5 pages, in Russian (Latin transliteration) and English.
- Les Livres Étrangers (Paris), 1932-1939; 1986-1991; n.d. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, questionnaires, etc.; some items are damaged. In French and Russian mostly. 15 items total.
- Lounz, Gregory (New York), April 1956; n.d. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  Contains 3 typewritten price lists in Russian (two of them use Latin transliteration).
- Lowood, Henry, Sept 5-6, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  Contains a printout of an e-mail exchange, 2 pages.